Contact

tammy_straps@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tammy-straps-msn-19650362 (LinkedIn) nursetamshifthappens.com/ (Blog)

Top Skills

Nursing Medical-Surgical Healthcare Management

Certifications

ANCC RN-BC Medical Surgical Medical Surgical

Honors-Awards

Good Samaritan Nursing Bronze

Tammy Straps MSN

Registered Nurse Manager @ Harris Health System Houston, Texas

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing, Inpatient Care, Medical-Surgical, Healthcare, and Healthcare Management. Strong healthcare services professional graduated from UT Arlington. MSN in leadership and Organizational Management.

Experience

Harris Health System 23 years 5 months

Nurse Manager April 2015 - Present (5 years 4 months) Houston, Texas Area

Registered Nurse March 1997 - Present (23 years 5 months)

Clinical Manager Medical Surgical Tele IMU

Gulf Coast hospital panama city Staff Nurse April 1995 - January 1997 (1 year 10 months) Panama City, Florida Area

Education

American Sentinel University

Master's degree, MSN Nursing · (2017 - 2019)

The University of Texas at Arlington

Bachelor of Applied Science - , Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2014 - 2015)

Lone Star College System
Associate of Science (A.S.) · (2002 - 2003)

Tom P Haney Technical Center vocational Nursing